A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3; 636.07 Cubic Feet 1659 containers - 1591 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
  - Clubs, 1962-1976; 6; 4.18 Cubic Feet 11 letter document boxes
    - Porcupine Club, 1960-1971 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Pot and Kettle Club, 1970 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Princeton Club of New York, 1962-1975 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - River Club, 1962-1976 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Country Club, 1962-1976 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Tarrytown Boat Club, Inc. University Club, 1962-1976 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - (The) Woodstock Golf and Tennis Club Associates, Inc., 1962-1976 (Box 199, Folder 2-3)
    - Woodstock Golf and Tennis Club Associates, Inc. - Finances, 1962-1975 (Box 200, Folder 1-3, Box 201)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1962-1976; 7; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
    - Colonial Williamsburg - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 201, Folder 4, Box 202, Folder 1-2)
      File includes a 1973 memoir by Francis T. Christy on the "Early Days of Williamsburg Restoration" (found in box 201, folder 4, Colonial Williamsburg A-D).
    - Annual Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Board of Trustees, 1964-1976 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Carter's Grove, 1962-1965 (Box 202, Folder 5, Box 203, Folder 1-6, Box 204, Folder 1)
    - J. R. Dilworth Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - 50th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Finances/Finance Committee, 1962-1973 (Box 205, Folder 1-3, Box 206, Folder 1-2)
    - Proposals, 1962-1968 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Printed Material (Box 207, Folder 1-2)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - By-Laws, Articles of Incorporation and Board of Trustees, 1970 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Finances/Finance Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Board of Trustees Minutes/Meetings, 1970-1976 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Minutes/Meetings (Box 208, Folder 3, Box 209, Folder 1-2)
    - Williamsburg Restoration, Inc. - Finances/Finance Committee (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Williamsburg Restoration, Inc. - Board of Trustees Minutes/Meetings (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Commercial Ventures, 1962-1976; 8; 8.36 Cubic Feet 22 letter document boxes
    - Commercial Ventures - A-C, 1965-1976 (Box 210, Folder 1-5)
    - Commercial Ventures - C-F (Box 211, Folder 1-5)
    - Commercial Ventures - G-L, 1965-1976 (Box 212, Folder 1-5)
    - Commercial Ventures - M-Q, 1965-1976 (Box 213, Folder 1-5)
    - Commercial Ventures - R-S, 1965-1976 (Box 214, Folder 1-5)
    - Commercial Ventures - T-V, 1965-1976 (Box 215, Folder 1-2)
    - Commercial Ventures - W-Z, 1965-1976 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - American European Associates, 1969-1971 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Capital Development Corporation, 1969 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Checci & Company, 1961-1969 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - The Fabric Tree, 1965-1971 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Fazenda Bodoquena, S.A. - General, 1963-1976 (Box 217, Folder 1-4, Box 218)
    - Fazenda Bodoquena, S.A. - Coelho Family, 1971 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Fazenda Bodoquena, S.A. - Financial Statements, 1970-1971 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Fazenda Bodoquena, S.A. - Printed Material (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Fazenda Bodoquena, S.A. - Reports, 1965-1972 (Box 219, Folder 4-5, Box 220, Folder 1)
    - General Development Corporation, 1965 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Groupement Immobilier Europen d'Etudes et de Participations (GIEP) - Correspondence and Corporate Papers, 1962-1971 (Box 220, Folder 3-4)
    - Inner City Merchandisers, 1970-1971 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Industrial Credit & Investment Corp. of India, 1962-1964 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Literary Productions, 1971-1974 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Mid City Developers, Inc., 1971 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - National Corporation for Housing Partnerships, 1968-1970 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Nigerian Theater Venture - General, 1962-1964 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Nigerian Theater Venture - Printed Material (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Orleans Farms Property - General, 1962-1971 (Box 222, Folder 1-3)
    - Orleans Farms Property - Reports, 1963-1976 (Box 222, Folder 4-5, Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Pakistan Industrial Credit and Investment Corp., 1962-1966 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Products of Asia (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Products of Asia - J. R. Dilworth Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Products of Asia - General, 1962-1966 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Products of Asia - Dynasty of Hong Kong Ltd., 1962-1971 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Products of Asia - Finances, 1962-1972 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Products of Asia - Board of Directors Meetings, Smiddy report, 1963 January 8 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Products of Asia - Minutes/Meetings, 1962-1965 (Box 224, Folder 3-4)
    - Products of India - General, 1962-1966 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Rouse Company - General, 1962-1966 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Rouse Company - Chicago Dock and Canal Co. Proposal, 1961-1963 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Simulamatics Corporation, 1966-1967 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Southern Corporation Development Fund, 1969 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Standard Oil Company (Ohio), 1968-1970 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Southern Cooperative Development Fund (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Banking - General - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 226, Folder 2-3)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - General - A-M, 1962-1976 (Box 227, Folder 1-4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - General - N-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 228, Folder 1-2)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - J. R. Dilworth, 1964-1976 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Minutes and Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Printed Material (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - South Africa, 1966-1968 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Building Industry - General, 1965-1968 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Building Industry - Structural Concrete Products, Inc. - Finances, 1962-1965 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Building Industry - Structural Concrete Products, Inc. (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Consultants, 1971-1974 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Electronics, 1962-1964 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Fuels, 1962 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Housing, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Imperial House, 1962-1964 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Insurance - General, 1965-1972 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Insurance - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America and College Retirement Equities Fund, 1962-1970 (Box 231, Folder 1-3)
    - Motion Pictures - General, 1963-1969 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Conservation, 1962-1976; 9; 114.95 Cubic Feet 290 letter document boxes, 9 legal document boxes and 1 legal tall box
    - Conservation - A-Z, 1
      - Conservation - A-C, 1962-1976 (Box 232, Folder 1-4)
      - Conservation - C-F, 1962-1976 (Box 233, Folder 1-4)
      - Conservation - F-L, 1962-1976 (Box 234, Folder 1-5)
      - Conservation - M-R, 1962-1976 (Box 235, Folder 1-5)
      - Conservation - S-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 236, Folder 1-4)
      - African Wildlife Leadership Foundation, Inc., 1963-1970 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - American Camping Association, 1969-1972 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - American Committee for International Wild Life Protection, Inc., 1962-1971 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - American Forestry Association, 1962-1969 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - American Rivers Conservation Council, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - American Shore and Beach Conservation Association, 1962-1976 (Box 237, Folder 6)
      - Anderson, Senator Clinton P., 1963-1967 (Box 237, Folder 7)
      - Australia, 1968-1970 (Box 237, Folder 8)
      - Appalachian Highlands Association, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Articles, 1962-1968 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Articles - Christian Science Monitor, 1966-1968 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Bahamas National Trust, 1965 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Books, 1964-1974 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Brumstead, Harlan B., 1963 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Business Proposals, 1962-1966 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Caribbean Conservation Corporation, 1962-1971 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Citizens Committee on Natural Resources, 1963-1971 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Conservation and Beautification Committee of the Tarrytowns, Inc., 1966-1971 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Conservation Center, 1965-1966 (Box 239, Folder 6)
      - Conservation Foundation - Contributions, 1962-1966 (Box 239, Folder 7)
      - Conservation Foundation - Board of Trustees, 1966-1968 (Box 239, Folder 8)
      - Conservation Foundation - General (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Conservation Foundation - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Conservation Foundation - Contributions (LSR) (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Conservation Foundation - Pinchot Conservation Institute and Education Center, 1962-1968 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Conservation Foundation - Pinchot Conservation Institute - Brandwein, Paul F., 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Conservation Foundation - Printed Material, 1966-1976 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Conservation Foundation - Train, Russell E., 1964-1969 (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - Conservation Proposals, 1962-1969 (Box 242, Folder 2)
      - Conservation Proposals - Cumberland, Island, Georgia, 1961-1967 (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - Conservation Proposals - St. Catherines Island, 1965 (Box 242, Folder 4)
      - East African Program, 1963-1967 (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - East African Program - Printed Material, 1963-1964 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - East African Program - Wirth, Conrad (trip), 1963-1964 (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - Education, 1966-1976 (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Environmental Ethics, 1964-1975 (Box 244, Folder 1-2)
      - Environmental Defense Fund, 1968-1977 (Box 244, Folder 3)
      - Environmental Policy Center, 1974-1976 (Box 244, Folder 4)
      - Environmental Teach-In, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 245, Folder 1)
      - Fabian, Harold P., 1961-1963 (Box 245, Folder 2)
      - Films, 1965-1969 (Box 245, Folder 3)
      - Gustafson, Carl O., 1959-1964 (Box 245, Folder 4)
      - Gustafson, Carl O. - Albright, Horace, 1961-1963 (Box 245, Folder 5)
      - Gustafson, Carl O. - Condolence, 1963 (Box 245, Folder 6)
      - Gustafson, Carl O. - Condolence - Mildred Layne Correspondence, 1963 (Box 245, Folder 7)
      - Gustafson, Carl O. - De Grazia, Alfred, 1959-1962 (Box 245, Folder 8)
      - Gustafson, Carl O.- ORRRC - Utah-Fabian, 1959-1961 (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - Holiday Awards, 1966-1969 (Box 246, Folder 2)
      - Hudson River Conservation Society, 1962-1971 (Box 246, Folder 3)
      - Humane Education Society, 1964-1965 (Box 246, Folder 4)
      - Indiana Dunes, 1962-1971 (Box 246, Folder 5)
      - Island Resources Foundation Anegada and Virgin Gorda Project, 1975-1976 (Box 247, Folder 1)
      - International Joint Commission of U.S. and Canada, 1971-1972 (Box 247, Folder 2)
      - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN), 1962-1972 (Box 247, Folder 3)
      - IUCN - Printed Material, 1962-1972 (Box 248, Folder 1)
      - IUCN - World Conference on National Parks, 1962-1964 (Box 248, Folder 2)
      - Keep America Beautiful, Inc., 1963-1971 (Box 248, Folder 3)
      - Kenya, 1964-1971 (Box 248, Folder 4)
      - Massachusetts Audubon Society, 1966-1976 (Box 248, Folder 5)
      - Meeman, Edward J., 1963-1973 (Box 248, Folder 6)
      - Jack Miner Migratory Bird Foundation, 1966-1973 (Box 248, Folder 7)
      - John Muir Institute - Auto Media Project, 1971-1974 (Box 249, Folder 1)
      - National Audubon Society - General and By-Laws, 1962-1976 (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - National Audubon Society - Contributions, 1962-1976 (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - National Audubon Society - Nature Centers Division, 1960-1971 (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - National Audubon Society - Nature Centers Division - Outhwaite, L., 1959-1962 (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - National Audubon Society - Nature Centers Division - Outhwaite, L. - Nature Center Handbook, 1962 (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - National Audubon Society - Nature Centers Division - Printed Material, 1960-1976 (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - National Audubon Society - Printed Material (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - National Clean Air Coalition, 1976 (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1960-1975 (Box 251, Folder 2-3)
      - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Printed Material (Box 251, Folder 4, Box 252, Folder 1-2)
      - National Wildlife Federation, 1963-1976 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - Natural Resources Council, Inc. - Allagash Region, 1962-1971 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council, Inc., 1970-1976 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Natural Resources Defense Council - Printed Material, 1975-1976 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Natural Science for Youth Foundation, 1962-1966 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Nature Conservancy - Contributions, 1972-1976 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Nature Conservancy - General, 1963-1976 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Nature Conservancy - Virgin Island Projects, 1969-1971 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Nature Conservancy - Printed Material, 1975 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - A-I, 1962-1976 (Box 255, Folder 1-3)
      - New York Zoological Society - J-Z, 1968-1976 (Box 256, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Administration Policy, 1961-1971 (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - African Wildlife Fund (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Aquarium - A-Z, 1962-1975 (Box 257, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Aquarium - Finances, 1962-1973 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Aquarium - Reports, 1967-1974 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Board of Trustees, 1963-1976 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - New York Zoological Society - Bronx Zoo - Legislation, 1962-1974 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - New York Zoological Society - By-Laws, 1968-1971 (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Clippings, 1972-1976 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Conservation Committee, 1969-1975 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Contributions (Miscellaneous) - A-Z, 1968-1971 (Box 259, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Contributions - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1971 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Employees, 1962-1970 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Finances, 1968-1975 (Box 260, Folder 1-2, Box 261)
      - New York Zoological Society - Fund raising, 1975-1976 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Legal, 1969-1971 (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Membership, 1969-1975 (Box 262, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Memoranda, 1968-1975 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Minutes/Meetings (Box 262, Folder 4-5)
      - New York Zoological Society - Annual Members Meeting, 1972-1976 (Box 263, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 263, Folder 3-7)
      - New York Zoological Society - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 (Box 263, Folder 8-10, Box 264, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - New York City - Parks Recreation and Cultural Affairs Administration, 1973-1975 (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Osborn, Fairfield, 1966-1971 (Box 264, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Planning Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 264, Folder 5)
      - New York Zoological Society - Printed Material, 1966-1976 (Box 264, Folder 6, Box 265, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1968-1976 (Box 265, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Laurance S. Rockefeller - Addresses, 1966-1971 (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - New York Zoological Society - Rockefeller University Institute of Research, on Animal Behavior, 1964-1970 (Box 265, Folder 5)
      - New York Zoological Society - Staff, 1969-1976 (Box 266, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Zoological Society - Whale Fund, 1968-1975 (Box 266, Folder 3)
      - New York Zoological Society - Wildlife Survival Center, 1970-1972 (Box 266, Folder 4)
      - Richard M. Nixon, 1968-1969 (Box 269, Folder 2)
      - North American Wildlife Foundation, 1962-1969 (Box 266, Folder 5)
      - Northern Plains Project, 1973-1976 (Box 266, Folder 6)
      - Open Space Action Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 266, Folder 7)
      - Orell, Bernard L., 1963-1967 (Box 267, Folder 1)
      - Palisades Nature Association, 1963-1970 (Box 267, Folder 2)
      - Puerto Rico, 1973 (Box 286, Folder 4)
      - Save the Redwoods League - Carl O. Gustafson, 1920-1961 (Box 1655, Folder 1-4, Box 1656)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc., 1965-1976 (Box 320, Folder 1-2)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Contributions, 1972-1973 (Box 320, Folder 3)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Finances, 1976-1977 (Box 320, Folder 4)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - A-Z (Box 320, Folder 5)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Contract Agreements (Box 321, Folder 1)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Contributions (Box 321, Folder 2)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Finances (Box 321, Folder 3)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial (Box 321, Folder 4)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Fund Raising (Box 321, Folder 5)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Fundraising - A-Z (Box 322, Folder 1-5)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Ground Breaking (Box 323, Folder 1)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Landscape (Box 323, Folder 2)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - National Park Foundation (Box 323, Folder 3)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Official Opening (Box 323, Folder 4)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial - Printed Material (Box 323, Folder 5, Box 324, Folder 1)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Mrs. L. B. Johnson Presentation, 1968 November 12 (Box 323, Folder 6)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Minutes/Meetings, 1965-1972 (Box 324, Folder 2)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Printed Material (Box 324, Folder 3)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Project Trail Blazers, 1967-1968 (Box 324, Folder 4)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Laurance S. Rockefeller Appeal Letters, 1965-1966 (Box 325, Folder 1)
      - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital Inc. - Youth Subcommittee (Box 325, Folder 2)
      - Southwest Research and Information Center, 1972-1975 (Box 325, Folder 3)
      - Sports Fishing Institute, 1967-1968 (Box 325, Folder 4)
      - U.S. Junior Chamber of Commerce National Conservation Program, 1960 (Box 325, Folder 5)
      - Vermont, 1972-1976 (Box 325, Folder 6)
      - Izaak Walton League of America, 1962-1971 (Box 325, Folder 7)
      - Izaak Walton League of America - Minutes - 41st Annual Convention and Conservation Conference - Cincinnati, 1963 June 12-15 (Box 326, Folder 1)
      - Water Pollution, 1960-1976 (Box 326, Folder 2)
      - Wilderness Society, 1963-1976 (Box 326, Folder 3)
      - Wildhorse Island, 1960-1961 (Box 326, Folder 4)
      - Word Wildlife Fund - Printed Material, 1972-1976 (Box 326, Folder 5)
      - World Wildlife Fund - Rockefeller, David and Laurance S., 1962-1976 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Parks, 2
      - Parks - A-Z (Box 267, Folder 3-4)
      - American Institute of Park Executives, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 267, Folder 5)
      - Council for Parks and Playgrounds, Inc., 1963-1968 (Box 267, Folder 6)
      - National Conference on State Parks, 1964-1974 (Box 268, Folder 1-4)
      - National Conference on State Parks - Constitution and By-Laws, 1966-1967 (Box 269, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - General, 1963-1976 (Box 269, Folder 3-4, Box 270, Folder 1-4)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - A-M (Box 271, Folder 1-3)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - N-Z (Box 272, Folder 1-3)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Annual Report, Executive Directorship, Policy, Presidency, 1966-1971 (Box 272, Folder 4)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Board of Trustees, 1966-1973 (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Booz, Allen, and Hamilton, Inc., 1965 (Box 273, Folder 2-3, Box 274, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Budget, 1966-1971 (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Committees, 1967-1970 (Box 274, Folder 3)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Conferences, 1966-1977 (Box 274, Folder 4)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Contributions, 1966-1971 (Box 274, Folder 5)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Constitution and By-Laws, 1965-1968 (Box 275, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Finances, 1966-1974 (Box 275, Folder 2)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Fund Raising, 1966-1971 (Box 275, Folder 3)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Memoranda, 1966-1971 (Box 275, Folder 4)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - History, 1964-1970 (Box 276, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Administrative Board, 1965-1967 (Box 276, Folder 2)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Board of Trustees, 1965-1976 1966 May 21 (Box 276, Folder 3-4, Box 277, Folder 1-3, Box 278, Folder 1-2)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Congress for Recreation and Parks, 1966 October (Box 278, Folder 3-4, Box 279, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Austin, Texas, 1967 April 14-15 (Box 279, Folder 2)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes/Meetings - Executive Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 279, Folder 3, Box 280, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - National Budget and Consultation Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 280, Folder 2)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Park Manual, 1965-1967 (Box 280, Folder 3)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - "Parks and Recreation", 1966-1971 (Box 280, Folder 4)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Personnel, 1966-1971 (Box 280, Folder 5)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2041
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Printed Material, 1971-1974 (Box 281, Folder 1-2, Box 282)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Projects, 1966-1970 (Box 282, Folder 3)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Public Affairs, 1965-1970 (Box 282, Folder 4)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Publication Proposal, 1974 (Box 283, Folder 1)
      - National Recreation and Park Association - Reports, 1964-1969 (Box 283, Folder 2)